(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the production, please be mindful of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS.
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots may be posted to social media.
Recording and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the production, please be mindful of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS.
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots may be posted to social media.
Recording and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin soon. Please wait a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the nature of the production, please be careful of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS.
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots may be posted to social media.
Recording and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly.
Please wait for a moment.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
PLEASE BE AWARE OF FLASHING LIGHTS THAT MAY
CAUSE DISCOMFORT AND/OR SEIZURES
演出の都合上
照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the nature of the production,
please be aware of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS,
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです。
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots may be uploaded to social media.
Audio/video recording and streaming are prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CALLIOPE: PINK / REINE: BLUE / BAELZ: RED
MARINE: RED / TOWA: PURPLE / OLLIE: RED
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the performance starts.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
PLEASE BE AWARE OF FLASHING LIGHTS THAT MAY CAUSE DISCOMFORT AND/OR SEIZURES FOR THOSE WITH PHOTOSENSITIVE EPILEPSY
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
For production reasons, please be careful of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS.
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Screenshots are OK to post on SNS.
Audio recording, video recording, mirror distribution, and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
Hi everyone! Are you ready?
We're hololive production!
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING: PLEASE BE AWARE OF
FLASHING LIGHTS THAT MAY CAUSE DISCOMFORT
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the nature of the performance,
please be aware of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS.
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです。
録音、録画、ミラー配信等は固く禁止いたします。
Uploading screenshots to SNS is allowed.
Recording and unauthorized streaming are prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS: MORI CALLIOPE (PINK) /
PAVOLIA REINE (BLUE) / HAKOS BAELZ (RED)
HOUSHOU MARINE (RED) / TOKOTOMI TOWA (PURPLE) /
KUREIJI OLLIE (RED)
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin shortly.
Please wait a moment.
演出の都合上
照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to production reasons,
please be aware of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS.
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
You may upload screenshots to social media.
Recording, mirroring, and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the show begins.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS,
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Posting screenshots to social media is allowed.
Recording and mirror streaming are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CONCERT STARTING SOON
ROD LAVER ARENA
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
PHOTOSENSITIVITY WARNING
演出の都合上
照明の点滅にご注意ください
Due to the production,
please be aware of flashing lights.
YOU ARE FREE TO TAKE SCREENSHOTS,
SCREEN RECORDINGS ARE NOT ALLOWED.
スクリーンショットをSNSにアップロード投稿OKです
録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固く禁止いたします
Posting screenshots to social media is allowed.
Recording and mirror streaming are strictly prohibited.
PENLIGHT COLOURS
CALLI LET ME SMELL YO FEET <3
hololive English COUNCIL
Let's go!
What is VTuber?
VTuber
Virtual YouTuber
Stream or create contents using 2D and 3D avatar
hololive production has over 70 female and male talents,
active in Japan, Indonesia, and English-speaking countries.
And has over 70 million YouTube subscribers
across all their channels.
Official streaming
Collabs
Singing
We're performing here today!
Have a great time!
Performer Introduction
Ahoy!
Captain of the Houshou Pirates! I am Houshou Marine~!
Konyappi!
hololive 4th Gen! I am Tokoyami Towa!
ZOMBANWA!!!!!
Super cute zombie idol, kuku- kuku- kuku- Kureiji Ollie!
Attention, please!
I am Pavolia Reine, the Wind Dancing Peacock Maiden!
What's up, Dead Beats
The Grim Reaper's first apprentice!
WAZZUP!
WAZZUP!!! It's everyone's global rat idol Hakos Baelz!
Are you ready?
Take off and fly!
Take off and fly...
The longer we wait...
The stronger it makes us...
...as we fight every fate.
Strength to finally defeat...
...this journey of a thousand years to me.
Yo everybody! What's up?
We are from hololive!
Are you ready to go on a journey?
Let's get started!
Stories told in gentle blue light.
Painted wishes grounded by the tide.
Longest paths connecting the dots.
Faint echoes of ages gone by.
Made a splash but found that I'm free.
A fish out of water, bound to the sea.
Though the reckless high tide brought you right by my side...
...I bet this moment's the wave we can ride.
Connecting songs across the sky.
Take off and fly...
The longer we wait...
The stronger it makes us...
...as we fight every fate.
Strength to finally defeat...
...this journey of a thousand years to me.
Witness the fire in our minds, burning inside...
...rising again from the ashes.
Every bruise and the scratches make us feel more alive.
We never give up, never give in...
...no matter what's ahead.
Instead we'll cast our worries aside.
There's no world for us to touch or to see.
We'll make it ourselves, then make memories.
There ain't a mystery our brains cannot solve.
We just shine brighter, grow tighter, evolve.
Connecting songs across the world.
Take off and fly...
The longer we wait...
The stronger it makes us...
...as we fight every fate.
Strength to finally defeat...
...this journey of a thousand years to me.
At the end of this world, where's our fighting chance?
Nothing's changing, it's always the same story...
...staged with a different dance.
Gotta have a happy end...
...for me, my friends...
...and those who've loved us until now.
I wanna see your smile...
...with you, somehow.
Take off and fly...
The longer we wait...
The stronger it makes us...
...as we fight every fate.
Strength to finally defeat...
...this journey of a thousand years to me.
Let's try, it can't be denied...
...the wish in my heart is you right here by my side.
Strength is all that we'll need...
...I won't wait a thousand years to meet.
Hi, the cutest zombie idol from hololive Indonesia, Kureiji Ollie here!
We have the fans here, can you sing along?
KU-RE-I-JI O-LLI-E!
え？私？
Eh? Me?
退屈な日常 このままでいいの?",
Boring daily life, is it okay like this?
通知待ってる携帯 見てばかりで
Just looking at my phone waiting for notifications
ほっと止まっていても 心震わせたい
Even if it's at a standstill, I want to make my heart tremble
これからがショータイム 歩き出していこうか
From now on it's showtime, shall we start walking?
One, two, threeで 星を見つけて
On one, two, three, find a star
Four, five, sixで 君を見つけたの
On four, five, six, I found you
Seven, eight, nineで 夢を見つめて
On seven, eight, nine, gaze at your dreams
Nine, four, zeroで 瞼が開くの
On nine, four, zero, your eyelids open
継ぎ接ぎ体に 溢れてくメモリー
Memories overflowing in my patchwork body
好き好き頭に 特効薬を頂戴
Please give my too-much-love head the ultimate medicine
次々脳内に ハッピーなメロディー
One after another, happy melodies in my brain
浮き浮きなパーティー Are you ready? Yeah!
A cheerful party, are you ready, yeah!
ドキドキ無い? それっ! すごい事なんて無いよ
No heartbeat? That! It's not a big deal
Shiny-Tiny-Snow 煌めいてよ舞台
Shiny-Tiny-Snow, sparkle on this stage
Crazy-Crazy-Dance 心躍るあなたに
Crazy-Crazy-Dance, for you whose heart is dancing
見つけてくれたジャーニー
The journey you found for me
Let's go!
SUPA!
MEGA!
HAIPA!
SISTA!
超かわいい 超ヤバい Crazy crazy crazy crazy...
So cute, so crazy, crazy crazy crazy crazy...
SUPA!
MEGA!
HAIPA!
SISTA!
超かわいい 超ヤバい Ollie Ollie Ollie Ollie
So cute, so crazy, Ollie Ollie Ollie Ollie
ぱったりんなこともたまにあんな
Bad luck happens sometimes
ぱったりんな雨が降ることもあんな
Bad rain falls sometimes
だけどIt’s all right 逃げてる暇はないTime
But it's alright, there's no time to run away
これからShowtime 虹もかかるよ
From now on it's showtime, a rainbow will appear
ドキドキするぐらい今が好きなの
I love this moment so much it makes my heart race
時忘れるぐらい熱狂して万歳
Let's go wild and celebrate until we forget time
体温剥がせるぐらいBPMは上限体
BPM is at the limit, enough to raise body temperature
再現のないこの期待みんなに共有したい
I want to share this limitless expectation with everyone
アストロノーツまでまだ足りない
Not enough even for astronauts
なんかこれもう三千世界
This is already the Three Thousand Worlds
主役間違いない団
No doubt about the main character
Put your hands up 満悦周回
Put your hands up, rounds of delight
ミラーボール反射するBlue light
Mirror ball reflects blue light
アンサンブルで丁々じゃない？
Isn't it a heated ensemble?
今夜誰も眠れないの Jollie Jollie Jollie night!
Tonight no one can sleep, Jollie Jollie Jollie night!
手と手繋ぎして一心同体 ぐんぐんマジで
Hand in hand, one heart and body, steadily, seriously
心三角 歓迎服従 Gimme gimme高く反応
Heart triangle, welcome obedience, gimme gimme, high reaction
覚悟は済んだHey? 耐え合うの強行体のRhyme
Are you prepared, hey? Enduring high-intensity rhyme
A to Z S級に後程 特急停心 Crazy
A to Z, class S later, special express heart stop crazy
ツギハギ体に詰め切っていた思い
Feelings packed into a patched body
カチコチハートに詰め込んだ願い
Wishes packed into a stiff heart
好き好きみんなに返してくよ愛に
I'll return my love to everyone who likes me
Jollie Jollie alright! Crazy party night!
ツギハギ体にあふれてくメモリー
Memories overflowing into a patched body
好き好き頭に特効薬を愛に
I love you, the medicine in my head is love
好き好き脳内にハッピーなメロディー
Happy melodies inside my head
ウキウキなパーティー Are you ready? Yay!
An exciting party, are you ready? Yay!
Jollie Jollie night ドレスコードなんてないな
Jollie Jollie night, there's no dress code
Shiny time 咲き乱れてくよ舞台
Shiny time, the stage is in full bloom
Crazy crazy dance 心躍らそうやJourney
Crazy crazy dance, let's make our hearts dance, journey
見つけた妥当正義な場所へ Let's go!
To the place I found, the correct and righteous place, let's go!
SUPA!
MEGA!
HAIPA!
SISTA!
超かわいい 超ヤバい Crazy crazy crazy crazy...
So cute, so crazy, crazy crazy crazy crazy...
SUPA!
MEGA!
HAIPA!
SISTA!
超かわいい 超ヤバい Ollie Ollie Ollie Ollie
So cute, so crazy, Ollie Ollie Ollie Ollie
Hey Jollie Jollie night! Let's crazy party night!
Stay up all night fun! Jollie Jollie Jollie yay!
Stay up all night fun! Crazy party night!
Hey Jollie Jollie night! Let's crazy party night!
Stay up all night fun! Jollie Jollie Jollie yay!
Thank you for listening! Bye-bye! WAAAA!!
ドキドキして Launch!
My heart is racing, launch!
Are you ready?
うんざいうんざい美少女はうんざい
Sick of it, sick of it, beautiful girls are sick of it
マリンは美少女
Marine is a beautiful girl
ねえ、いいよね？年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, it's okay, right? Age doesn't matter, they say
そういう面倒くさいのも含めて愛してくれるって？
You'll love me including all that troublesome stuff?
ねえ、言ったよね？言ってない？ふん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hey, you said it, right? You didn't? Hmph, so you say that
ちなみにこの船では「美少女無罪」が適用されますけど
By the way, on this ship, the "beautiful girl innocence" rule applies
任せて 魔法で若返る
Leave it to me, I'll rejuvenate with magic
秘密の素顔は君にだけ
I'll show my secret form only to you
Only for you!
あたし厄介よ 皆となんかじゃ
I'm troublesome, compared to others
はしゃげないわ 近頃は
I can't frolic lately
宝の島にしてほしい気分
I feel like making it a treasure island
出航！
Departure!
ぎゅっとして美少女無罪
Hold me tight, beautiful girl innocence
君の一番 目立ちたい
I want to stand out as your number one
やったらホントは自信ないけど 頑張っちゃう
I'll do it, actually I'm not confident but I'll try my best
キュッキュッキュルン
Kyu kyu kyurun
恋する気持ち 17歳
Feelings of love, 17 years old
てっぺんになっちゃうわ 大人の時間
I'll reach the top, it's adult time
ドキドキして Launch!
My heart is racing, launch!
まだ早い
It's still early
だだだだめですか フリルの服着たら
Is it-it-it no good if I wear frilly clothes?
Go for it!
だだだで魔法少女になってみたい
I-I-I want to try being a magical girl
ギリギリ有罪
Barely guilty
17歳ミリな積極性
17 years old, millimeter of aggressiveness
せっかく君も もっと若い子
Since you're also with a younger girl
なんだってするから 見捨てないで君たち
I'll do anything, so don't abandon me, you guys
ちょっと言ってみてみたい
I want to try saying it a bit
たまにいじけて
Sometimes I get sulky
それでもいいの？
Is that okay too?
年頃だもん 本気にしちゃう
I'm at that age, I'll take it seriously
仲間！
Comrades!
宇宙！ Come with me!
Universe! Come with me!
シュッバーン！
Shubban!
ハートにジャブ びしょびしょジャムザイ
Jab to the heart, soaking wet Jam-zai
アレ アレ 年下 連続
Oh my, oh my, younger ones one after another
「さよなら」なんて言っちゃって
Saying things like "Goodbye"
構ってくれる君が好き
I like you for looking after me
きゅっきゅきゅるん きゅっきゅきゅるん
Kyukkyu kyurun kyukkyu kyurun
優しくしてね 17歳
Be gentle, okay? 17 years old
ツッコミ 経験値 お楽しみ中
Retort experience points, currently enjoying
ドキドキしてるー？
Is your heart racing?
あーっ！ お許しください
Ah! Please forgive me
このマリンの魅力 魔力 不可抗力
This Marine's charm, magic, force majeure
罪な女ね
I'm a sinful woman, aren't I?
離さないで 捕まっていて
Don't let go, hold on tight
世界の色 さ 見せてあげるから
Because I'll show you the colors of the world
ギュッと 合わせて びしょびしょジャムザイ
Hold tight together, soaking wet Jam-zai
君の1番 狙い出して
Aiming for your number one spot
いけたら
If I can
冗談も 大好き だけど 真剣よ
I love jokes too, but I'm serious
きゅっきゅきゅるん きゅっきゅきゅるん
Kyukkyu kyurun kyukkyu kyurun
恋する気持ち 17歳
The feeling of being in love, 17 years old
ヘンになっちゃうわ 大人の時間
I'm going crazy, it's adult time
ドキドキしてるー？ まだ早い
Is your heart racing? It's still too early
ムザイ！ ムザイ！ びしょびしょジャムザイ
Innocent! Innocent! Soaking wet Jam-zai
マリン！ マリン！ マリンはムザイ！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
夜空キラキラ 待っててクラクラ
The night sky is sparkling, waiting and feeling dizzy
Ahoy! Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine desu!
Ahoy! Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine here!
How are you guys feeling?!
You doing good?
She's speechless! Hahaha.
I am speechless!
ちょっと待って。マイクが、マイクが。
Wait a second. My mic, my mic.
どこどこ？
Where is it?
Well, while she's figuring that out, uh, should we do introductions?
見つけた！
I found it!
Oh, I can speak again!
Oh, she's back!
We good.
Hi! I'm alive, which is ironic.
Hey everybody, what's up?!
Hey guys, I guess we should do an introduction.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! You go first, you go first.
I guess because I am Senpai, here I go.
皆さーん！
Everyone!
It's me, Mori Calliope from hololive English!
Hardworking Shinigami reaper-rapper-singer.
Nice to meet you! What's up?
Who is that?
Who am I?
Wassup!!
I am Hakos Baelz!
Your local Aussie rat has come home!!
I am Baelz from hololive English! Witness me!
Witness!
Witness me!
Witness! Alright!
So, some of you may already know, I think a lot of you already know of us,
but I'm gonna tell you a little bit about VTubers for those that don't know.
So, let me clear something up.
Not AI! We're not AI!
We're not AI! No, no, no!
We are many things.
Um, we are singers, dancers, performers.
A lot of us are gamers.
I know some of you guys are gamers.
You gamers? You gamers?
Gamer here, gamer there. I see them everywhere.
But, but the main thing is, we are REAL!
We just look like this.
We are real! Yeah!
Like any other performer or, you know, singer, dancer, gamer, etc.,
we are real people. We just look like this.
That's the only difference, right?
Hee-hee! And we belong to hololive production!
Anyone know hololive production?
You know us?!
Yes! And for those who don't know,
hololive production is a virtual idol agency that is based in Japan,
but we are also reaching overseas!
We want to become worldwide!!
Yeah, worldwide!
I have a question, though.
Yes.
Are you guys having a good time so far?!
And how about you guys watching on the stream?
Oh yes! We know a lot of you guys are watching.
We see you! We see you! There you are!
Oh, yeah! 見てくれてありがとうございます！
Oh, yeah! Thank you for watching!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
...です。
...I'm looking forward to it.
Calli, we made it.
We did.
We're in Melbourne!
Oh my god, it's a real place!
Are you sure?
We're in Melbourne.
They didn't just fly us somewhere else, like, maybe a different...
...like, some place like, like off of like, normal map?
No, it's real. It's real. We're real. They're real.
Or they just take us to London or something like that?
Did you say Mel-bin?
What was that? Did you say Mel-bin?
Melbourne.
Mel-bin.
What?!
Is there something wrong with the way I said Melbourne?
Mel-bin.
Melbourne.
What? What's wrong?
You've got to give me something, Bae. You've got to give me something.
What am I saying?
Uh, you're doing it perfectly, right guys?
It's Mel-bin. It's Mel-bin. It's Mel-bin. It's Mel-bin.
Am I saying it better now? Mel-burn?
No. Mel-bin. Mel-bin. Mel...
...burn?
Yeah, close enough.
Alright.
But yeah, we've arrived in Melbourne...
...and we're so excited to be here!
That's right. There's a lot of stuff here, actually.
Yes, there is!
There's like art all over the place...
...and like, really good food.
Yes! The chicken's so good!
The chicken is so good!
Um, yeah. So, Melbourne is known for a lot of things.
But if you know me...
...obviously caffeine is my jam.
For those who are new to Melbourne, I highly encourage you to check out all the coffee shops...
...'cause the coffee is the best in Mel-burn!
But yeah, please do check out Melbourne if you guys have the chance. There's a lot of cool things...
...a lot of museums, galleries, and plenty of fun experiences for you to try!
That's right.
Also, speaking of loving chicken, hey, you in the crowd...
...who did like the TakaMori like fanart of me and Kiara like kissing thing...
...you're not going to get away with that. I'm just letting you know you're not getting away.
Good job. Good job. Good job.
Hey, I told you, good job.
Don't encourage them!
Anyway, anyway, we do have a bit of sad news.
Yes, we do have sad news for you guys.
Um, the sneak peek part of the show...
...is unfortunately ending here.
But for those on stream who want to see more...
...please buy the ticket at SPWN on this one if you guys want to keep watching.
Uh, for you guys at the venue, don't worry about it.
Yeah, you guys don't have to do anything.
Just sit there and have fun, okay?
Yeah! And so as for everybody else that's going to come along with us...
...let's keep it going!
Yeah! Woo!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!
SNEAK PEEK HAS ENDED
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended!
Thank you for watching!